[Music]
the pandemic has posed some serious
challenges in the finance sector and to
help them navigate through these
turbulent times we bring you india risk
practitioners a special segment as a
part of india risk management awards
the corona virus pandemic is a complex
multifaceted crisis has resulted in
giving rise to various risks and
highlighted the importance of risk
management
so the first response to the pandemic
was really how do we preserve and
protect what we have the focus being
that since we didn't know what the
future held how do we manage what we
already held had and how do we make sure
that we create the right kind of
resilience in the organization to be
able to
survive the short term which was a 12 to
18 month period
the second was really regrouping
for what we believed would definitely be
a bounce back that as there was a
cure for the or a vaccine for the virus
and as vaccination programs took shape
how do we basically prepare for what
would be
a resurgence or a bounce back in the
economy itself and therefore in our
businesses
and the third is really how do we look
at taking advantage of what would be
an opportunity available to our
businesses
in a landscape where there are a lot of
players who will be hurt
and many players who may not survive
well to nominate your organization for
the india risk management awards visit
the below link